Yes, when does the bank refund you the fraud money,
how does it happen that if a fraud happens with you then the bank
will refund you the money here, the fraud
money that you will get, you will not have to deposit this bill, watch
this video completely
and you have to understand everything, see here
many people get defrauded at this time
and there they think that if
I will register a complaint then
I will not have to deposit the bill here, some people
think that now I have been defrauded, I will have to
deposit the money here, so brother you should
understand this here, if there is no fault of yours in committing fraud then
brother you will
not have to deposit the bill here, the bank will
pay all your money here, you will
not have to do anything, under what conditions does the bank
pay the money and under what conditions do you have to
pay the money here, you should
understand everything in details and I request you to watch the
video completely and you have to
understand everything, I myself have been defrauded,
brother I have refunded my money here, so under
what conditions will the bank refund me the money
here  If a refund has been given to you, then brother, under what
conditions will the bank refund the money? See,
you get defrauded online as well as
offline. Here,
you get defrauded in both ways.
How have you been defrauded offline? Sometimes, like
your credit card etc. gets debited here, then the
fraud happened from there, so is
it called offline there? And
like online, if there is a fraud through a call
or someone calls you and you get
defrauded through that, then it is an online fraud. Here,
fraud happens without OTP
and fraud happens here even without OTP.
You share the OTP on some website,
fraud happens through that too.
You get defrauded from many places,
but the main thing you have to understand is that the fraud has happened,
now will the bank refund the money or will
I have to pay it myself and under what conditions does the
bank give a refund? I am going to
cover everything in details. Before that, you should like the
video and
subscribe to the channel because you keep getting information on my channel.
Let me
talk.  I am going to do it, see here, for this
I have made a lot of proper videos,
how you can get a refund of your fraud money, you will get the
refund of the fraud money in your bank account within 7 days, I will
give a lot of videos at the end of this video,
you can go there and watch the video,
how you
can get a refund of your fraud money, that too within 7 days,
not a lot of time, in some conditions the
refund is given in 24 hours and
in some conditions the money is refunded in a day, you will
find a lot of videos on my channel,
now I am going to talk about when the
bank refunds you the fraud money here,
or if a fraud has happened, then it deposits the bill to you here, the
bank does not refund you,
let's understand everything carefully, okay,
in the first number I am going to talk about you getting
defrauded, okay, you getting defrauded, then
what happens here, when you get
defrauded, then here, like it happened through a call
or you shared the OTP, if a
fraud has happened here, then here  Let me tell you,
if you share the OTP here,
what happens here, what does the bank do here,
when you share the OTP, it means it is
your mistake, the bank does this
here, sometimes some banks
give you a refund of Rs.50, you have to
deposit the amount yourself and there are some banks which do
not give you the money even for Rs.50, you have to pay the entire bill here,
see how it is done here, like
here you have shared the OTP,
in this condition it is your mistake brother
because you have shared the OTP brother, the bank
gets a reply because you got
defrauded after sharing the OTP, so here
in the condition the bank sometimes gives you the
money for Rs.50, sometimes the bank does not give even Rs.1,
you have to pay the entire bill, understand this here
and I am going to talk about the second number,
like here you did not share the OTP,
you logged in to some website,
there was a fraud, so what does the bank do there also, the
same bank condition comes there too
brother, you have my credit card
How did you add it here, then the bank would have taken it there, that is,
see, there is no fault of the bank, the
fault lies with you here, it is
your fault for sharing the OTP and if
you added your credit card on any website, then it is
also your mistake, so here
in that condition also the bank raises its hands here and clearly
tells you that it is not my fault,
see here when you register a complaint etc., the
bank will clearly fold its hands and say that it is
not my fault, you have done all this, you have
shared your credit card on this website, due to this the fraud happened, you shared the
OTP and everything that happens through the website is done by the
bank, now when does the bank refund your money,
you understand carefully, everything is
fine, see here when there is a fraud with you,
you did not share the OTP or did anything,
then the bank refunds your money 100%
because it happened with me
myself, I was cheated, I had an ADAC
credit card, I was cheated,
right when I was cheated, I
I am also going to
tell you further how I registered my complaint. Watch the video completely.
How does one register a complaint?
When I registered my complaint,
after that, within 24 hours,
whatever amount of money was defrauded from my credit card was added
here. Why was it added?
Brother, it was
not my fault here, I mean, it was not this small mistake of mine.
Money was defrauded from my credit card.
See, someone got to know my credit card number
and he
started committing fraud. I received an OTP but
I did not share the OTP. My
credit card was defrauded automatically. Brother, I did
not share the OTP automatically. It was defrauded
without OTP.
When my credit card was defrauded without
OTP,
I registered my complaint here.
After that, whose fault was it in this? It was the bank
's fault. Why brother, it was the bank's fault.
Therefore, it was the bank's fault. When brother, I did
not share the OTP nor did I add my credit card to any other website, then
how did the fraud happen? It was the bank's fault. That is why the
bank did not send me here.  100% of the money was refunded to me,
whatever fraud happened with me,
all the money was refunded to me within 24 hours,
okay, if it is not your fault, then the
bank will refund you 100% of the money here,
you will not have to pay a single rupee here,
if it is your mistake, then some
banks give you 50% here and some
banks do not give you even 1 rupee, okay,
if it is your mistake, okay, here there are
many banks which give 50%,
but many banks do not give even %, do
not give rupees, you have to pay the entire bill,
but if there is not even a single mistake of yours, then
you will get 100% refund, like I
got it and you will also get 100% refund,
now how do you have to register a complaint,
let's first number I am going to
tell you how to register a complaint,
first number you have to block your credit card,
like if there is a fraud with you,
first number you have to call the number which is on the back of the credit card,
right from the
customer's  You have to
register a complaint and
block the credit card. The first task is that
you have to
process all this within 24 hours. The second
task is to go to your nearest police station from where the
fraud happened with you.
You have to make an application. Okay, secondly,
what you have to do is to submit an application to your police
station. As soon as you have been
defrauded, you have to take a receipt from the police station. Second and
third task is that every bank has a
dispute form here. No matter
which bank's credit card you have, all of them have a dispute form.
You have to
download that
form here. You have to get a printout of that
dispute form from any online shop. You have to fill that dispute form there.
Okay, you will have to give all your details there.
Fill the dispute form.
After filling the dispute form, you have to get a photocopy of the
copy of the FIR that you got from the police station.
After attaching both, convert it into a PDF.
Okay, what about both the police station
copy that you have and the dispute form
that you filled?
You have to convert a PDF. When you
convert the PDF, you will get a
mail ID below in the dispute form,
so you have to mail it
from your registered mail ID. In that you have to mail the dispute
form and a copy of the application you gave to the police station.
All this
process has to be done within 24 hours.
When you mail, you will
get a reference number from there.
Your complaint has been made there and 1930 is used,
you have to do that too. If it is used with anyone then do it. If it is
not used with anyone then no
problem, you have to complain on 1930.
All this has been done in cyber crime.
Now all your
processes have been done here for three-four times.
Everything is done within 24 hours. And one more thing
you will do if you
go to twitter4j, brother, it will not be a message but they will
call you there. Many frauds also
live with you there. If someone is
mentioning his number there, fraud
people mention it there. If he talks to you privately, then not only will
he talk to you but also the bank.
No, don't check it in any other private way brother,
Bluetooth etc. Everything is installed, you have to talk to the bank whose
credit card you had after
checking all this,
after talking there what you have to do is they will
call you themselves, you will
share your number, so when they call,
after that tell them that I have been
defrauded in such a way, it is not my fault,
such and such fraud has happened, when you
tell all this, after that if not a single mistake of yours is found, then
all your money will be refunded within 24 hours or 7 days,
if you make even the slightest mistake there, like
you shared your OTP, gave your credit card on some website,
your complaint keeps
going on there for a month or two, when it keeps going on there, then the
bank
decides whether you have to pay Rs. 50
or you have to pay everything, then the bank will
decide itself, but if there is not a single mistake of yours, then
I 100% say that you will get your money in
full, if you make even the slightest
mistake, then your money will be refunded to you at Rs. 50 or
in some case you may not even get a refund, but  If there is
no mistake, I guarantee that the bank
itself is responsible for refunding the money.
This was the entire process.
Perhaps you have understood everything now, under what
conditions the bank refunds you
if you are defrauded. If you
want information about how you have to
process everything, you will find all the
videos here. Click and
watch the video and you will have to understand everything, how
you had to register the complaint, how to
do what, so you will be able to understand everything in details. In
this way, you
can get your fraud money refunded and I have
covered everything in details here. If you like the
video, then like it and
subscribe to the channel. You keep getting information like this on my channel. Let's meet
in the next video.